const content = [
    {
        question: "What year was the Philadelphia Eagles founded?",
        answers: ["1925", "1978", "1933", "1960"],
        correctAnswer: "1933"
    },

    {
        question: "Who is the current owner (2019) of the Eagles?",
        answers: ["Jerry Jones", "Howie Roseman", "John Lynch", "Jeffrey Lurie"],
        correctAnswer: "Jeffrey Lurie"
    },

    {
        question: "How many Super Bowl titles does the Eagles have?",
        answers: ["1", "0", "6", "3"],
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },

    {
        question: "Which Eagles head coach won the most games?",
        answers: ["Doug Pederson", "Andy Reid", "Chip Kelly", "Dick Vermeil"],
        correctAnswer: "Andy Reid"
    },

    {
        question: "How many Super Bowl appearances does the Eagles have?",
        answers: ["4", "0", "3", "2"],
        correctAnswer: "3"
    },

    {
        question: "Which Eagles quarterback is the All-time passing leader in franchise history?",
        answers: ["Nick Foles", "Donovan McNabb", "Ron Jaworski", "Randall Cunningham"],
        correctAnswer: "Donovan McNabb"
    },

    {
        question: "Which Eagles running back is the All-time rushing leader in franchise history?",
        answers: ["Lesean McCoy", "Duce Staley", "Ricky Watters", "Brian Westbrook"],
        correctAnswer: "Lesean McCoy"
    },

    {
        question: "What year did the Eagles win their first Super Bowl?",
        answers: ["1980", "1995", "2004", "2018"],
        correctAnswer: "2018"
    },

    {
        question: "What is the name of the current stadium of the Eagles (2019)?",
        answers: ["Heinz Field", "Soldier Field", "Lincoln Financial", "Super Dome"],
        correctAnswer: "Lincoln Financial"
    },

    {
        question: "What division does the Eagles play in?",
        answers: ["NFC East", "AFC North", "NFC South", "AFC West"],
        correctAnswer: "NFC East"
    }
];